Guide to the Lucy Kramer Cohen Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- November 2009 Acquisition, 1902-2005; 35; (36 boxes)
  - "Poultry and egg report" press release and Wall Street Journal article, circa 1947 (Box 15)
  - Professional correspondence and personal financial documents, 1947-1956 (Box 15)
  - Arthur Lazarus correspondence and reports regarding "reduction-in-force", circa 1953 (Box 16)
  - Research and correspondence for loyalty investigation, 1950; 2 (Box 16)
  - Clippings and printed material related to Labor Board work, 1950s; 3 (Box 16)
  - Washington Human Relations Area Files, Inc. newsletters and notes, 1955-1956 (Box 16)
  - Washington Human Relations Area Files, Inc. memoranda, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Human Relations Area Files, Federal Republic of Germany, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Human Relations Area Files, Republic of Korea, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Human Relations Area Files, Iran, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Working file from reports procedures, 1953 Mar 13 (Box 16)
  - Training Program, 1952 Dec 1-10 (Box 17)
  - Conference - Special Farm Labor Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - Census of Agriculture, draft of Memo, 1953 Mar 19 (Box 17)
  - McCarran Act, Bureau of Employment Security, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - Merson Field Staff Meeting, 1952 Dec 23 (Box 17)
  - Materials missing from files, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - Average hourly earnings, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Bibliography, 1952 Dec 12 (Box 17)
  - Texas Re-Survey, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - State Reports & Analysis Representatives Conference, 1952 Dec (Box 17)
  - Projects, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Article - Labor Market, Prevailing Farm Wage Program, 1952 (Box 17)
  - Perquisites, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - Opening Wage Reports, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Status of Wage Submittals, 1953 (Box 17)
  - 6 months program - Farm Wage Analysis Section, 1952 (Box 17)
  - Progress reports, 1953 (Box 17)
  - "Highlight" Monthly Reports to John B. Ewing, 1943 (Box 17)
  - Government Prevailing Wage Programs, I. Sabghir's Study, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Staff Meeting, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - Lucy Kramer's Memoranda to Staff, William Mirengoff, etc., 1953 (Box 17)
  - Mexican Nationals - cut-off points re: Prevailing Wage Program, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Mexican Nationals - Distribution in Total Farm Labor Force, 1951-1952 (Box 17)
  - Seasonal Requirements of Foreign Workers, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Farm Wage Studies, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Sampling Studies, Procedures, Evaluations, etc., 1952 (Box 17)
  - Office Memoranda, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Revision of 1952-1953 Prevailing Wage Activities (Box 17)
  - Farm Revisions, Rules of Thumb, etc., 1952 (Box 17)
  - Farm Labor Fact Book, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Office Studies (Farm Wage Analysis Studies), 1953 (Box 17)
  - Sources, etc., 1950s (Box 17)
  - Interdepartmental Committee on Children and Youth (Migrant), 1953 Mar 31 (Box 17)
  - Meetings, 1952 (Box 17)
  - Wage Studies, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - Crop - Wage Areas (Box 17)
  - Work for L. Bean, 1954 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Labor Board Documents, 1951-1953; 2 (Box 17)
  - "Bimonthly Summary of Labor Market Developments in Major Areas," Census Labor Data, 1952 Sep (Box 17)
  - Drafts of Farm Wage Progress Reporting Analysis and Procedures, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1955 (Box 17)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research Inc., memoranda and correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 17)
  - L. Bean, 1954 Jan (Box 17)
  - Health Department appreciation certificate, 1978 Mar 1 (Box 18)
  - "Industrial Relations Research Association", 1953 Dec 28-30 (Box 18)
  - Retirement party materials, correspondence with C. Everett Koop, 1989 Jun 28 (Box 18)
  - Retirement party photographs, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Post-retirement plans, correspondence with Cappie Morgan, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence and paperwork related to first retirement, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Personnel correspondence and financial documents, 1978-1981 (Box 18)
  - Government service correspondence, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Lucy Kramer employment, Public Health Service, 1971-1981 (Box 18)
  - Public Health Service, employment, retirement, 1975-1987 (Box 18)
  - Service recognition awards for 25 and 30 years, 1970s-1980s (Box 18)
  - Public Health Service work, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Publications, 1958-1978 (Box 18)
  - Bureau of Health Professionals, contract listings, 1986-1971 (Box 18)
  - Public Health Services, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Smoking memo, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Analytical Policy Advisory Committee, 1988; 2 (Box 18)
  - Analytical Policy Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Editing work on "Meeting Medical Manpower Needs", 1968; 3 (Box 18)
  - Women in the medical profession, 1968 (Box 18)
  - "The Fuller Utilization of the Woman Physician", conference materials, 1968 (Box 18)
  - "The Fuller Utilization of the Woman Physician", conference materials, 1968; 2 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence regarding woman physician conference, 1968 Nov 16 (Box 19)
  - Health Department reports on family planning, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Labor Department wage analysis report, 1946 (Box 19)
  - Health Benefit Plans, special work for secretary, 1946; 2 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Labor Department documents, 1944-1947; 2 (Box 19)
  - Helen Gahagan Douglas, "Cost of Living Speech" and other related material, 1948 Apr (Box 19)
  - Helen Gahagan Douglas, campaign materials including signed photograph, 1946-1951 (Box 19)
  - Helen Gahagan Douglas, writings and clippings, 1940s-1950s; 2 (Box 19)
  - Puerto Rico correspondence, 1963 Aug (Box 19)
  - Department of Agriculture research materials, re: dried skim milk, circa 1938 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous notes, 1943-1954 (Box 19)
  - Clippings and notebooks, 1963 (Box 19)
  - "Franz Boas' contributions to physical anthropology" from Journal of Physical Anthropology, v.6, n.2, 1948 (Box 19)
  - Indian Self-Rule Conference, 1983 (Box 19)
  - National War Labor Board, Alaska salmon industry transcript, 1944 May 12-13 (Box 19)
  - National War Labor Board, Alaska Salmon Industry Hearing, 1944 May 11 (Box 19)
  - Handbook of Labor Statistics, 1950 (Box 20)
  - Health Department notes, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence and outline for book on Puerto Rico, 1962-1964; 2 (Box 20)
  - Indian Self-Rule Conference, correspondence and materials, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Indian Self-Rule Conference, correspondence and notes, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Indian Self-Rule Conference, correspondence, 1983 Apr 12 (Box 20)
  - Indian Self-Rule Conference, correspondence and notes, 1953-1983 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence and photocopies of 1982 edition of Handbook of Federal Indian Law, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Felix Cohen Memorial Home, correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 20)
  - "Manpower Resources Program"; "HEW and You" v. 14, n. 7 and 8, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - Lucy Kramer CV, 1967 June (Box 20)
  - Public Health Service publications, notes, and employment correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 20)
  - Course notes: linguistics, 1932-1937 (Box 20)
  - Course notes, 1940 (Box 20)
  - Course notes, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Course notes, 1953 (Box 20)
  - Course notes: linguistics, probability, 1933 (Box 20)
  - Book borrowing records and address lists, 1930s (Box 20)
  - Course notes: anthropology, statistics, 1932 Autumn (Box 20)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare art exhibit, photograph and ribbon, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, personnel papers, 1960s (Box 20)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, personnel paper, 4 (Box 21)
  - Course notes, 1920s 1930s (Box 21)
  - "The Price Study" report no. 11 (2 copies), 1935 Jun 1 (Box 21)
  - Vitamin B research on dried skim milk, 1938 (Box 21)
  - Social Science Research Council, "A Survey of Research in the Field of Industrial Relations", 1928; 2 (Box 21)
  - Children's clothing sizes, 1937 Jun 28 (Box 21)
  - Notes and research materials on the stature of 3/4-year-olds, 1930s (Box 21)
  - Art notes and clippings, 1962-1966 (Box 21)
  - Volunteer work for the National Symphony Orchestra, 1962 (Box 21)
  - Key School newsletters and Parent-Teacher Association material, 1950-1954 (Box 21)
  - Course notes, Russian, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Key School newsletters, 1952-1954 (Box 21)
  - Washington Watercolor Association newsletter, 1981-1997 (Box 21)
  - Art show materials, 1970s (Box 21)
  - First aid class notes and assignments, 1951 (Box 21)
  - Proofread manuscript, circa 1954 (Box 21)
  - University of New Mexico banquet, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Spanish notes, 1940s-1950s (Box 22)
  - Deerwood Adirondack Music Center, draft of correspondence, 1953 (Box 22)
  - Draft of correspondence to Ted Sorenson; resume of Hyman Bornstein, circa 1962 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence, legal and financial documents regarding ownership of 1722 H Street NW, 1949; 2 (Box 22)
  - Franklin School activities (Box 22)
  - Personal projects and writings, 1962-1991 (Box 22)
  - Funeral services for Annie Frankel Kramer; art exhibition pamphlet, 1965-1970 (Box 22)
  - Washington Watercolor Association newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - American Sign Language notes and clippings; letter of reference, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Affidavits, 1950s (Box 22)
  - Publishing correspondence, 1970 (Box 22)
  - "Americanizing the White Man," reprint, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Robert J. Montalbano, 1998-1999 (Box 22)
  - Ian Frazier, "Great Plain" and accompanying correspondence, circa 1996 (Box 22)
  - Beinecke correspondence and annotated galleys, 1990s (Box 22)
  - Indian Self-Rule Conference, correspondence, publicity materials and photographs, circa 1983 (Box 22)
  - Joel Cornwell, "From Hedonism to Human Rights: An Interpretation of Felix Cohen's Last Words", 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - University of New Mexico Law School, thank-you letter, 1981 (Box 22)
  - "The American Indian" with tribute to Felix Cohen, 1954 (Box 22)
  - New Mexico voting rights case, 1948-1998; 2 (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs board, 1960s-1980s (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, clippings and memoranda, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian affairs annual meeting, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, correspondence and notes, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, Portland meeting, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, correspondence, 1992; 2 (Box 22)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Michael Trujillo, documents supporting nomination for Indian Health Service Directorship, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs Full Board meeting, 1993 April (Box 23)
  - Indian Affairs Newsletter, 1993; 2 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs Executive Director search, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Indian Affairs Newsletter, correspondence and notes, 1963-1975 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affaris, memorandum, 1994 May 26 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs History project, 1993-1996 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, correspondence, publicity mailings and memoranda, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs history, correspondence, 1993-1994; 3 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, 1995; 2 (Box 23)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, meeting notes, 1981-1985 (Box 23)
  - Pine Ridge, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Home for the Elderly dedication, 1963-1965 (Box 23)
  - Pine Ridge, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Home for the Elderly dedication, 1963-1965; 3 (Box 24)
  - Leonora Rosenfield's death, 1982 Jan 11 (Box 24)
  - Selma Friedman Levy memorial service, 1995 Feb 5 (Box 24)
  - Miriam Zales Kramer death and obituary, 1982 April 30 (Box 24)
  - Tributes- S. Levy, J. Senturia, Annie Frankel, T. Herzel, 1972-1998; 2 (Box 24)
  - Robert A. Hecht, "Oliver LaFarge and the American Indian: A Bibliography, 1991 (Box 24)
  - Pearl Bronz Holly, 1982 Jun 2 (Box 24)
  - Joseph Senturia, 1992-1994; 4 (Box 24)
  - "Indian Law at a Crossroads," University of Connecticut School of Law, 2005 (Box 24)
  - Richard Schifter, clippings and transcript of talk given at Tali Alter's Bar Mitzvah, 1984-1992 (Box 24)
  - Morris Raphael Cohen Library dedication photographs, 1953 May 3 (Box 24)
  - Résumés, 1960s-1970s (Box 24)
  - Norman Thomas, 50th anniversary of 1932 presidential race, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Barnard-in-Washington Networking Directory, 1994 Summer (Box 24)
  - Annotated empty envelope, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous projects, articles of interest, 1949-1995 (Box 24)
  - 90th Birthday Cards, 1997 (Box 24)
  - 90th Birthday Cards, 1997 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence, circa 1992 (Box 25)
  - Review of "Cohen's Handbook", Catholic University Law Review, 1971 Fall (Box 25)
  - Cohen Revision, University of New Mexico, 1977 (Box 25)
  - Ruth Richards Eisenstein Eulogy, 1997-1998 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Mishnun Hardman's 90th birthday, 1999 March 7 (Box 25)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1987 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence and Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence and clippings, 199-2000 (Box 25)
  - 80th birthday tribute, 1987 (Box 25)
  - Charlotte T. Walkup Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 25)
  - Medical and disability documents, 1997-1998 (Box 25)
  - Joseph Mindel, "The Frog Tree", 1975 (Box 25)
  - Photograph, correspondence and reprint of legal article, 1950-1954 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence with Sam Hirsch, 1999 (Box 25)
  - Margold project for Robert Montalbano, 1999 (Box 25)
  - Purmia Bhat introduction to grandmother's autobiography, 1998 (Box 25)
  - Photographs of the Felix S. Cohen Exhibit in the Interior Department Library, 1954 (Box 25)
  - Letter and paper from Jill E. Martin, 1996 (Box 25)
  - Jill E. Martin correspondence, 1998 (Box 25)
  - Jill E. Martin correspondence, including two articles by Felix S. Cohen, 1998 (Box 25)
  - Jill E. Martin correspondence, 1999 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence with Tom Dublin, 1998 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 25)
  - Peter Taylor correspondence, 1995 (Box 25)
  - Dahlia Tsuk correspondence, 1996 (Box 25)
  - Felix S. Cohen correspondence with Eleanor Roosevelt (2 copies), 1941 (Box 25)
  - Winnebago Agency clipping (photocopy), 1935 (Box 25)
  - Clippings and notebooks from Felix S. Cohen's papers, circa 1962 (Box 25)
  - Materials used for Felix S. Cohen's biography, 1953-1954 (Box 25)
  - Photocopies of clippings, 1925-1926 (Box 25)
  - Bob Graham correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
  - Balsam Bay correspondence and legal documents, 1996-1998; 5 (Box 25)
  - Arthur Lazarus speech at Yale, 2000 March 31 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Ethical Systems and Legal Ideals, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Notes, clippings and materials used in The Legal Conscience, circa 1960 (Box 25)
  - Materials related to the publication of The Legal Conscience, 1960s (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous material related to The Legal Conscience, 1953-1960s (Box 25)
  - American Indian Policy Review Commission, correspondence and memoranda, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Donation of Felix S. Cohen papers to Yale, circa 1990 (Box 26)
  - Printed material by and in honor of Felix S. Cohen, 1954-1956 (Box 26)
  - Yale periodicals, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Beinecke library acquisition of Felix Cohen Papers, 1990-1992 (Box 26)
  - Tributes and obituaries, 1967-1997; 2 (Box 26)
  - Joseph J. Senturia festschrift, 1992 Spring (Box 26)
  - Aaron Kramer estate, 1970s (Box 26)
  - Correspondence with Aaron Kramer, 1974 May (Box 26)
  - Beinecke Library, Register for the Felix S. Cohen papers, 1991 (Box 26)
  - "A Letter and a Spring of My Existence", Jill E. Martin, 1995 (Box 26)
  - "Inventory of Federal Programs supporting Health Manpower Training", 1972 (Box 26)
  - "Inventory of Federal Programs that support Health Manpower training 1970", 1970-1974 (Box 26)
  - "Training Health Science Workers: The critical challenge", 1966 (Box 26)
  - Health Services, printed material, 1959-1997; 9 (Box 26)
  - "Health Resources Statistics", 1975 (Box 27)
  - "A Study of Health Services & Facilities in the Adirondack Preserve", circa 1970 (Box 27)
  - "A Study of Health Services and Facilities in the North Country", circa 1971 (Box 27)
  - Health Services, printed material, 1958-1967 (Box 27)
  - Public Health Service Superior Service Award, 1976 (Box 27)
  - Public Health Reports (Health Insurance), 1958-1969; 2 (Box 27)
  - "Third Annual National Conference on Public Health Training", 1967 August 16-18; 2 (Box 27)
  - Social Work Manpower and Pharmaceutical, section directory (Box 27)
  - "Administration of Community Health Services", 1961 (Box 27)
  - Public Health Services, printed material, 1957-1970 (Box 27)
  - Personnel final papers, 1977 (Box 27)
  - Manpower Resources, personnel correspondence and material, 1966 (Box 27)
  - Personnel documents including Curriculum Vita, 1970s (Box 28)
  - Workshop on Health Manpower Shortages, 1976 Nov 9 (Box 28)
  - Health Manpower Shortage, 1976; 2 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous Health Department and Manpower documents, 1981-1982 (Box 28)
  - "Health Manpower Shortage Areas", 1974; 2 (Box 28)
  - Health Manpower papers and reports, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
  - Quentin R. Remein, "Improving Federal Health Programs Addressed to Health Scarcity Areas", 1976 (Box 28)
  - Annotated "Inventory of Federal Programs that Support Health Manpower Training", 1970-1972 (Box 28)
  - Health Department papers and reports, including two prepared by Lucy Kramer, 1959-1964 (Box 28)
  - Name Labels, 1982 Jul-Aug (Box 28)
  - Correspondence with Pietro Lazzari and press releases, 1966-1967 (Box 28)
  - Pietro Lazzari, photographs, 1968 (Box 28)
  - Mock-up and plates for "Carbonizzati", 1967 (Box 28)
  - Bust of Eleanor Roosevelt, photographs and correspondence, circa 1965 (Box 28)
  - Empty envelope labeled "Elizabeth Drewry Hyde Park" (Box 28)
  - "Retirement Life," periodical, 1965 Oct (Box 28)
  - Pietro, Evelyn, and Nina Lazzari, photographs, 1960s (Box 28)
  - Pietro Lazzari
    - Correspondence and clippings, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
    - Photographs and prints, 1956-1963 (Box 28)
    - Professional correspondence, 1965; 3 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence regarding purchase of the bust of the head of Norman Thomas, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence regarding bust of the head of Eleanor Roosevelt, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and publicity material, 1965-1968 (Box 29)
    - Photocopies of Italian correspondence, 1967 (Box 29)
    - Obituary, 1979; 2 (Box 29)
    - Biography, 1965 Nov (Box 29)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Bust contributors' list, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Photographs, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and biography, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and Auction poster from the Gallerie Internationale in New York, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and photographs, 1965-1992 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and photograph, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, clippings and photographs, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Notes and clippings, including obituary, 1960s-1970s (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, clippings and photographs, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Writings, photographs and reproductions, circa 1978 (Box 29)
    - Solicitation of bust of Eleanor Roosevelt, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Photographs and clippings, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Walter Ruther correspondence, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 29)
    - Writings and statistical reports, circa 1968 (Box 29)
    - 651 notes and statistical reports, 1968-1969 (Box 29)
    - Wang Ming Gallery, Washington D.C., press release and draft, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Empty envelope, circa 1967 (Box 29)
    - Photographs, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and photographs, 1965; 2 (Box 29)
    - Empty envelope, circa 1969 (Box 29)
    - Notes and press release, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Photocopied correspondence, circa 1965 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and clippings, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Address cards, 1960s (Box 30)
    - Address cards, 1960s (Box 31)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - Biographical material, 1967 (Box 32)
    - Sketch of Norman Thomas bust, undated (Box 32)
    - Eugene Debs award dinner, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Debs Foundation correspondence, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence related to bust of Pope Paul VI, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Norman Thomas and Eleanor Roosevelt correspondence, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, clippings and notes related to the bust of Eleanor Roosevelt, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Clippings, 1967-1971 (Box 32)
    - Clippings from Italian publications and photographs, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Publicity materials and sketches, circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - Early shows, correspondence and clippings, 1963-1965 (Box 32)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt bust, correspondence and clippings, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt bust, Dohor correspondence, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Manuscripts; description of a dream, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Annotated empty folder, 1960s (Box 32)
    - Photographs of Lazzari's acceptance of prize for bust (Box 32)
    - Norman Thomas acceptance speech drafts and copies, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Press release concerning exhibit, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Directory index cards, 1969; 2 (Box 32)
    - Personal correspondence, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Carbonizzati correspondence, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt bust, correspondence and clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 32)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt bust, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 32)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt bust, correspondence, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous clippings and publicity materials, 1963 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence and publicity materials, 1962-1963 (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous notes, clippings and publicity materials, 1960s (Box 33)
    - Correspondence, press releases and biographies, 1963 (Box 33)
    - Clippings and photographs related to publicity, 1926-1965 (Box 33)
    - Photographs and clippings, 1965 (Box 33)
    - Adlai Stevenson Bust, correspondence, 1966 (Box 33)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt, correspondence, 1964 (Box 33)
    - Miscellanea and correspondence, 1965 (Box 33)
  - Washington Watercolor Association Newsletters, ¹1972-1995; 2 (Box 33)
  - Stamp collection, 14 (Box 33)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration Service Award Medals, 1970s-1980s (Box 33)
  - Health Resources Administration Administrator's Special Citation, 1980 June 27 (Box 34)
  - Columbia scholarship certificate, 1924 (Box 34)
  - Association of American Indian Affairs audiocassettes of oral histories and speeches, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Norman Thomas Tribute Audiotape reel, 1965 Sep 23 (Box 34)
  - Monthly Labor Review, Vol. 64, 1947 January-June (Box 35)
  - University and high school diplomas, house floorplans, 1920s-1950s (Box 36 Oversize)
- June 2014 Acquisition, circa 1900-2003; 8.54; (13 boxes) + 7 record albums
  This accession is roughly organized into four groupings: correspondence, awards and certifications, photographs, and audiovisual materials.
  - Correspondence, circa 1900-2003
    - Family correspondence, 1926-1936 (Box 37)
    - Family correspondence, 1930s-1990s (Box 38)
    - Family and other correspondence, 1900-1970s (Box 39)
    - General correspondence, 1923-1936 (Box 40)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes fraternity brother correspondence.
    - General correspondence, 1933-1941 (Box 41)
    - General correspondence, 1940s-2003 (Box 42)
      Includes holiday cards from colleages and friends from Yale.
    - Condolences for Felix Cohens death, 1953 (Box 43)
    - Address files, 1940s-1960s (Box 44)
  - Awards and certifications, 1930s-1990s
    - Awards presented to Felix Cohen, with related photographs and other papers, 1930s-1990s (Box 45)
    - Felix Cohen's bar certifications, 1949-1961 (Box 46 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, 1930s-1980s, undated